NO ENTRY
(진입금지)
Leave it to me!
나한테 맡겨
That took long enough. I can finally take a nap.
이제 낮잠 좀 자도 되겠네
I told you not to rush to the front line.
전선에 가지 말라고 했을 텐데
Our mission was to stop the Others's advance.
괴이가 다가오지 못하게 막기만 하라고
Yes...
예…
Sorry, Captain Shiden.
죄송합니다, 시덴 대장님
Well done, Captain Shiden.
고생했어, 시덴 대장
You should take a break sometimes, Captain Shiden.
너도 게으름 좀 부려봐, 시덴 대장
Shut it.
됐거든
I knew I'd become a captain someday.
언젠가는 대장이 될 거라고 짐작했어
Train the new recruits and pay attention to their performances,
신입 교육하고 소대원들 케어하는 게
those are what a captain does.
대장의 임무지
Kasane was supposed to be the captain.
원래는 카사네가 대장이어야 하는데
Do you want her to take your place?
바꿀 생각은 없어?
Not a chance.
뭔 소리야
Besides, she got her hands full already.
카사네도 해야 할 일이 있는데
I can't ask her to take over the platoon.
바꾸긴 뭘 바꿔…
What are you discussing?
뭔 얘기 중이야?
What brings you here?
여긴 어떻게 왔어?
You're not working here today, right?
오늘 작업하는 곳 여기가 아니잖아
I'm here to submit a progress report.
진도 보고하러 왔어
I heard you discussing me.
무슨 얘기 하고 있었는데?
It was nothing.
아무것도 아니야
We were talking about what makes a good captain.
어떻게 하면 좋은 대장이 될 수 있을까 의논 중이었어
Do you have other plans today?
다른 스케줄 있어?
Yuito is coming here today.
오늘 유이토가 오기로 했어
I'll go pick him up.
데리러 가봐야 해
Thanks.
고마워
Kasane, it's been a while.
오랜만이야, 카사네
It's nice to see you again.
오랜만이네
You seem to do very well.
많이 좋아보인다
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫Felling of tiredness is losing yourself♫
나른해 losing yourself
♫How do you still create a relationship each other♫
관계를 이룰 방법을 못 찾은 건가
♫It’s my awkward friend’s fault♫
귀찮은 친구가 있어
♫Until death, wanting someone somewhere to embrace me♫
죽을 때까지 누군가의 포옹을 원해
♫While the devil is not here and between the chaos♫
겨우 숨 돌리는 혼돈과 허무함 속에
♫Aiming between win and lose♫
승리와 실패 사이에 목표를 둬
♫Not to be running out of patience for now, I’m trying to be careful♫
믿음을 벼랑 끝으로 몰지 마 조심해
♫You’ll see I’m always on your side♫
You'll see I'm always on your side
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
오늘도 죽을힘을 다해 연락해
♫You’re frigid and your roller coaster inside the brain♫
네 머릿속 차가운 궤도에 말이야
♫The grungy days and the unprecedented catastrophy♫
흔들었던 날들에는 없는 재난
♫Where is the glory buried?♫
영광은 어딘가에 묻어둔 지 오래
♫The lonely monster in a moment♫
이 순간 외로운 야수가
♫The bullet shot by the machinegun goes parallelly♫
날아드는 탄알과 함께
♫To pierce with the theory♫
세상의 모든 이치를 꿰뚫어
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
오늘도 죽을힘을 다해 연락해
♫The bullet shot by the machinegun goes parallelly♫
날아드는 탄알과 함께
♫I tried hard to connect today as well♫
오늘도 여전히 함께해 똑똑히 연락해
♫You’re frigid and the theory in the brain♫
네 머릿속 차가운 정의에 말이야
"EVERYONE'S FUTURE" It's not being used anymore, don't worry.
(각자의 미래) 이제 괜찮으니까 무리하지 마
You should listen to your doctor.
순순히 의사 말을 듣는게 좋을 거야
Did you choose to do this?
진짜 네가 원해서 그러는 거야?
Yes.
그래
Where is Arashi?
아라시는?
She said this place was too noisy to take a nap.
여기가 너무 시끄러워서 잠이 안 온대
Are you here for the retirement paperwork?
소대 탈퇴 수속을… 밟으러 온 거야?
I also came here to check on everyone.
모두에게 인사도 하고 겸사겸사
I see a lot of new faces around here.
낯선 얼굴들이 많네
There have been many new recruits.
신입이 많이 들어왔으니까
The Extinction Belt is gone,
단절의 띠가 사라지긴 했지만
but there are still come remaining Others.
괴이는 여전히 존재하잖아
I heard Shiden became a captain.
시덴 너 대장으로 승급했다며
How are you doing?
괜찮은 거냐?
I'm doing just fine.
물론이지
I'll become a major general or even the chief.
앞으로 연대장도 될 거고 본부장도 될 거야
You? As the chief?
본부장이 될 거라고?
The tension between Suoh and Seiran has never ended.
스오와 세이란 사이의 대립 문제가 아직도 팽팽하잖아
There should be more cooperation between the two cities.
서로 도시간의 합작을 깊이 해야 할 필요가 있어
The people will be in a lot of trouble if someone who doesn't know it becomes a leader.
그 중요성에 대해 모르는 인간을 상사로 모시면 사람들에게 피해가 클 거야
I plan to keep going on missions before I received the official retirement order.
난 퇴역 명령이 떨어지기 전까지 계속 임무를 수행할 거야
I'll make sure OSF won't go astray again.
토벌군이 또 다시 잘못된 방향으로 걸어가는 일은 없어야 하니까
I feel relieved with you guys around.
너희가 있으니 마음이 놓여
You're welcome to drop by anytime.
언제든지 보러 와도 돼
Should we throw another dumpling party?
간만에 군만두 파티 어때?
Suit yourself, just don't order too much food.
좋지, 너무 많이 주문하지는 말고
To the destruction of Kunad Gate, cheers!
쿠나도 게이트가 사라진 걸 위하여
Cheers!
위하여
The dumplings were delicious,
군만두가 아주 맛있긴 하지만
but there were too many of them.
그날은 진짜 너무 많이 주문했다고
You ate plenty of them yourself.
너도 많이 먹었잖아
I don't waste food for no good reason.
난 음식 낭비하는 거 싫어해
Have you seen Hanabi?
하나비는 만나봤어?
No, I haven't.
아니 아직
Alice Platoon will be on patrol missions.
앨리스 소대가 순찰 임무를 수행할 거라던데
Go to her now if you want to see her.
만나려면 서두르는게 좋을 걸
You're right. Thanks.
그러네, 고마워
Alice Platoon...
앨리스 소대…
Hanabi, Tsugumi.
하나비, 츠구미
Yuito.
유이토
How is your family?
너희 고향은 괜찮아?
Regarding the inhumane experiment conducted at the OSF hospital,
토벌군 병원에서 실시된 비인도적 실험에 관해
-the chief of the hospital has... -What my uncle did at the facility
-해당 병원장인… -삼촌이 병원에서 한 일은
was never known to my parents.
우리 부모님도 모르더라
They were more worried about me, actually.
오히려 날 더 걱정하셔
There is a challenging future ahead for the Ichijo family.
이치조 가문이 앞으로 힘들어질 지도 몰라
But perhaps that's for the best.
그래도 이만큼인게 다행이라고 봐야지
But things are even tougher for Captain Alice.
하지만 앨리스 대장 처지가 많이 곤란할 거야…
That's because the Chairman of OSF hospital
토벌군 병원의 이사장이
is Captain Alice's elder brother.
앨리스 대장의 오빠이니까
How are you holding up, Yuito?
유이토 넌 좀 어때?
Chief Sumeragi has been replaced.
스메라기 본부장님이 짤렸어
Based on his statement during the hearing,
형이 공청회에서 증언을 해서
he will face punishment.
처분을 받은 것 같아
The Extinction Belt may be gone now,
단절의 띠를 제거했지만
but the Sumeragi family has faced public uproar.
스메라기 가문은 여전히 엄중한 비판을 받고 있어
But still, we cannot dwell on the past.
그래도 영원히 과거에서 살 수는 없는 일이니까
I agree.
나도 그렇게 생각해
Even though I was scouted into the OSF,
스카웃을 받고 토벌군에 합류했지만
but fighting along everyone
너희 모두와 함께
and creating a better future for the sake of New Himuka
대중들을 위해 뉴히무카가
is still very meaningful.
더 좋은 미래로 향하도록 분투해서 좋았어
After the Extinction Belt has been eliminated,
단절의 띠가 사라진 뒤로
the sunlight has become warmer.
태양이 예전보다 더 따뜻해진 것 같은 기분이야
The plants are very happy.
식물들도 엄청 기뻐해
I will do my best to give them
모두가 조용히 지낼 수 있도록
a peaceful life.
난 계속 노력할 거야
Kasane, Yuito,
카사네, 유이토
how are you holding up?
몸은 괜찮아?
I heard you are retiring. We're going to miss you.
소대를 탈퇴한다며, 너 없으면 많이 외로울 것 같아
Yuito, check this out.
유이토, 내 말 들어봐
Major General Fubuki and Captain Alice
후부키 연대장과 앨리스 대장이
are finally getting married.
곧 결혼할 거래
The marriage was arranged a long time ago.
우린 오래전부터 혼약이 정해진 거라
It's not really that big of a surprise.
그러니까 놀랄 필요는 없어
We'll be sure to attend your wedding.
결혹식에 꼭 참여할게요
I'll make the bouquet for you.
부케는 제가 만들게요
Well, that is one way to say it...
물론 좋지… 하지만
Yeah, now is not the right time for a wedding.
응, 아직 결혼식을 치루기에는 좀 그래
You can invite only the people from HQ.
우리 본부 구성원들만 참석해도 되잖아요
I'll consider that idea.
고민 좀 해볼게
Yuito, Kasane, see you around.
유이토, 카사네, 다음에 봐
You people are always so noisy.
조용할 틈이 없네
Arashi...
아라시
I'm glad you're finally discharged, Yuito.
퇴원 축하해, 유이토
Well, that's one burden taken off my shoulder.
이제 나도 한시름 놓을 수 있겠어
You must be really worried about Major General Fubuki.
사실 연대장이 엄청 걱정되는 거 맞지?
I don't have the time to be concerned about his business.
난 걱정따위 할 시간이 없어
Congratulations on the promotion, Major General Luka.
연대장이 된 걸 축하해
Are you really retiring?
진짜 소대를 탈퇴하는 거냐?
What will you do next?
그럼 앞으로 뭐 할 건데?
I'm going to college.
대학에 입학하려고
I want to learn more about the world.
공부를 하고 싶어
I see.
그래
I'm going to do my best
나도 능력을 최대한 발휘해서
to help make this country a better place
토벌군의 신분으로 의무를 다 할 거야
as a member of the OSF.
이 나라를 바꾸기 위해 열심히 일해야지
What is your plan?
바꿔? 어떻게?
This country is not a friendly place for Bell Peppers.
이 나라가 벨&nbsp;페퍼에 대한 시선이 안 좋아
Our system has ignored them completely.
그 사람들의 생활에 대한 관심이 전혀 없어
We pretend like they don't exist at all.
존재하지 않는 사람마냥
Without brain power, they can't see anything.
뇌능력이 없으면 아무것도 못 보잖아
I had gone through that as a kid.
나도 어릴 때는 그랬어
In order to develop my power,
결국 초뇌능력 개발을 위해
I spent every day inside the lab
매일 실험실에 갇혀서
and suffered in loneliness.
혼자 고통스럽게…
-Luka? -What's wrong?
-루카 -왜 그래?
Wait...
아니…
I think there was a boy just like me who was also a test subject.
나랑 같은 피실험자인 남자애가 있었던 것 같아
I managed to survive those experiments thanks to him.
그 애 덕분에 고통스러운 실험을 견딜 수 있었는데
But now, I can't even remember his name.
난 그 아이의 이름조차 기억이 안 나
I see.
그렇구나
Anyway, let's hope for the best for everyone.
아무튼 다들 힘내자
Yes.
그래
You too, Kasane. We don't know how the project will go,
카사네 너도, 그 계획이 어떨지 모르겠지만
but don't push yourself too hard.
너무 무리하지는 말고
Yeah, I understand.
응, 알았어
It seems everyone has really forgotten him.
다들 진짜 기억이 안 나나봐
They don't remember anything about Karen.
카렌을 기억 못하고 있어…
On that day, history was rewritten.
그날, 역사가 바뀌었다
We did it, Fubuki.
성공했네, 후부키
Alice...
앨… 앨리스…
Why are we the only people who remember Karen?
왜 우리만 카렌을 기억하는 걸까
Is it because we connected ourselves to Yuito and Kasane through SAS?
SAS로 유이토와 카사네랑 연결해서 그런 건가?
Just like the wielder of Red Strings,
레드 스트링스 뇌능력자와 같이
we have become the people who can observe the world.
우리도 세상을 관측하는 사람이 된 거지
Yuito, how is your body holding up?
유이토, 몸은 좀 어때?
Don't worry about me.
걱정 마
I stopped having headache after that day.
그 이후로 두통이 사라졌어
I can use my power with no problem.
초뇌능력도 쉽게 시전할 수 있고
Is it because the Kunad Gate has been destroyed?
쿠나도 게이트가 사라져서일까?
Whatever the case is, this is great.
아무튼 너무 잘됐어
Yeah.
그래
Yes, keep it up.
좋아, 바로 그렇게 하는 거야
Hanabi, a little to the front!
하나비, 조금만 더 앞으로
Yes.
네
I still can't get used to having Alice in the team.
난 아직 앨리스가 있는 세상이 낯설어
What are you talking about?
뭔 소리야?
She's been here since you joined the force.
네가 입대할 때부터 함께 했는데
You may be from the other platoon, but...
네가 아무리 다른 소대에 있었다지만…
She's always been here...
앨리스는 원래 여기에 있었거든…
What were we talking about just now?
우리 방금 뭔 얘기를 한 거야?
You mentioned the causality between Karen's time jump
카렌이 타임 점프한 거랑 앨리스가 아직 살아있는 게
and Alice being alive all this time.
뭔가 관계가 있는 것 같다고 했지?
Did you find anything else after that?
그 뒤로 아무 진전이 없어?
In other words, the incident caused a massive butterfly effect.
아무튼 큰 나비효과를 일으켰지
But we have no way to prove it.
증거는 없지만
He sacrificed himself to create a miracle.
자신을 헌신해서 기적을 만들었달까…
Who sacrificed himself?
누가… 기적을 만들었다고?
It's Karen.
카렌이
Karen?
카렌
I guess that's it.
그런 것 같아
But I don't like making baseless assumptions.
난 근거 없는 결론은 싫어
Karen is slowly being wiped from everyone's memories.
아마 카렌이 점점 사람들의 기억에서 사라지는 건가봐
You are right.
그러게…
At this rate...
이러다가는…
Yuito! Yuito!
유이토…
In the end, only we remember the whole story.
결국 우리 둘 외에는
Karen has been erased from everyone's memories.
아무도 카렌을 기억하지 못하고 있어
This is the world he wanted to create.
이게 바로 카렌이 원했던 세상인가봐
Other than Alice being alive,
앨리스가 여전히 살아 숨 쉬고
everything else remains unchanged.
다른 건 모두 예전과 같아지는 것
Even so, I still think Karen's was wrong.
그래도 난 카렌이 옳다고 생각하지 않아
Changing the history for the sake of a loved one
누군가를 위해 역사를 바꾸는 건
should not be allowed.
허락 받으면 안되는 행위였어
The world has changed.
세상이 바뀌고
But still, we are alive.
우리는 살아남았고
Karen was the one who created this reality.
지금의 역사를 만든 사람이 카렌이라고 해도 과언이 아니지
But we will
하지만
create the future for ourselves.
미래를 만드는 건 우리가 될 거야
Yes.
맞아
We'll create our own future.
우리의 미래를 만드는 거야
Sorry for the long wait.
오래 기다렸지?
Thanks.
고마워
Fubuki.
후부키
Who is that coffee for?
그거 누구 주는 거야?
Kasane, you are still a soldier of OSF.
카사네 너 아직 토벌군에 계급장 남아있는 거지?
Yes. I'll retain my ranks until the other preparation is complete.
응, 저쪽에 준비 완료될 때까지는 그대로야
The saviors of our country are here.
구국영웅 나오셨네
Or should I say "traitors?"
아니다, 반역자라고 해야 하나?
Kagero and Kyoka?
카게로, 쿄카
I'm glad to see you're doing well, Yuito.
많이 좋아보이네, 유이토
Are you two taking part in the Moon investigation?
두 사람은 달측 조사 계획에 함께하는 거야?
Yes. The New Himuka government wanted our help.
맞아, 뉴히무카에서 부탁했어
We disbanded the Togestsu Faith too.
토게츠교도 해산시킬 겸
When BABE stopped operating, the cryosleep devices also stopped.
베이브가 멈출 때 냉동 수면 장치도 작동이 멈췄나봐
All the immigrants from Moon woke up.
잠들어있던 이민단도 전부 깨어났어
Without BABE, they are not a threat.
베이브가 없으면 그 사람들은 아무것도 못하거든
The government has no records of you two being Togetsu spies.
정부의 두 사람이 간첩이었다는 기록이 사라졌어
It was a deal between the adults.
큰 일 하는 사람들끼리 거래를 한 거지
They will require the knowledge and information you have.
두 사람의 지식과 정보가 필요하다는 뜻이지
Yes. If the information we have can help in any way,
그래, 우리의 정보가 도움이 된다면
the government will have our full support.
힘껏 도울 거야
And Yuito, regarding our father...
유이토, 네 아버지 일 말인데
My father...
우리 아빠?
Chairman Sumeragi knew about those inhuman experiments.
스메라기 의장님은 인도적이지 못한 일들을 다 알고 있었어
But he also protected New Himuka from Togetsu.
하지만 뉴히무카가 토게츠의 침해를 받지 않게 보호하셨어
We will spread the word around.
이것도 모두 우리가 전달할 거야
Thank you, Kyoka.
고마워, 쿄카
Kagero, what will you do
조사 계획이 순조롭게 진행된다면
if everything goes well after the project?
카게로는 뭐 할 거야?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이야?
Will you go back to the Moon if you can?
달로 돌아갈 수 있다면 돌아갈 거야?
I no longer have the intention to go back there.
돌아가고 싶은 마음은 사라진지 오래야
Don't you have a reason to go back there?
달에 대한 아쉬움 같은 건 없어졌어?
I am concerned about
달에 두고 온 가족들
my family on the Moon
지금의 달의 상황
and what the place has become.
이 모든게 많이 신경 쓰이지만
But there is no way to go back there just yet.
돌아갈 수 있을지 모르겠어
I'm glad Kagero decided to help.
카게로가 도와주겠다니 정말 다행이다
You are at the top of the command chain of the immigrants,
이민단이 그래도 군대 중의 최고 사령관이니까, 그렇지?
General Shin Daniel.
신 다니엘 장군님
Don't call me that.
그렇게 부르지 말라고
Isn't that your real name?
카게로 본명인 거지?
We are counting on you, General.
잘 부탁해요, 장군님
People from ancient times can be such a pain in the neck.
고대인들 진짜 귀찮아 죽겠네
They left behind all those files.
자료를 잔뜩 남겨서는 진짜
What was that, General?
뭔 소리십니까, 장군님
Nothing.
별거 아니야
What's wrong, Hanabi?
쿄카, 왜 그래?
Is there no way for Yuito's power...
유이토의 초뇌능력이…
It can't be restored.
회복 가능성이 없다는 얘기지?
If we could stop it back then...
그때 우리가 막을 수 있었다면…
It wouldn't make a difference.
막아도 소용 없었을 거야
Without Yuito, all of this...
유이토가 없었다면 아마 지금쯤…
I know that!
물론 알아
But what is wrong with Kasane?
하지만 카사네도
What is she thinking anyway?
대체 뭔 생각을 하는 걸까
Are you really going to the Moon?
진짜 달에 갈 거야?
Yes, I want to be there.
그래, 갈 거야
I'm worried about Kasane too.
나도 카사네가 너무 걱정돼
Is she really going to the Moon?
달에 가겠다던데 진짜야?
There are a lot of technologies and information left behind by the immigrants in Togetsu.
토게츠에 이민단의 기술과 자료가 남아있거든
We have the resources.
그걸 사용할 수만 있다면…
However...
그래도…
We don't know what the Moon has become.
달의 지금 상황이
The worst case is that it's now crawling with Others.
최악의 경우 이미 괴이가 지배하는 세상으로 되어있겠지
Even so, Kasane insists on going there.
그래도 카사네 의지는 변함 없어
She's even going there alone.
게다가 혼자 가다니
I heard that you volunteered to be the advance team.
선발대에 들어가겠다고 자원했다며
We don't know how it is on the Moon.
달의 상황을 모르니까
So I must take point.
일단 내가 가봐야 할 것 같아
We can just send the drones.
무인 관측기를 보내면 되잖아
You don't have to...
왜 굳이 네가…
If I run into people who are attacked by Others,
괴이한테 습격받은 사람들 중에
I can save them with my power.
초뇌능력이 있는 사람이라면 구조될 수 있어
Someone must go there first.
그래서 누군가는 가야 해
But still...
하지만…
I hate that feeling.
나 너무 억울해
I don't want to have any regret.
더이상은 후회하고 싶지 않아
I won't just stand and do nothing while people die.
누군가 목숨을 잃어가는 걸 보고만 있지 않을 거야
Not anymore...
그러기 싫어…
Kasane...
카사네
I knew this would happen to you.
난 네가 지금처럼 될 거라는 걸 알면서도
But I insisted on making you fight
네가 싸우러 나가도록 부추겼어
and made you responsible...
네가 책임을 짊어지게 했다고
I...
나… 난…
I hate that feeling as well.
나도 억울하긴 마찬가지야
I just can't accept it!
진짜 너무 억울해
Nagi and I had a promise.
나기랑 약속했는데
We promised to become great soldiers.
훌륭한 토벌군이 될 거라고 말이야
But why...
그런데 난 왜…
Yuito.
유이토
I'm sorry, I...
미안한데 나…
I don't want to have any regret.
나도 후회하기 싫어
I've made up my mind.
나 결정했어
Kasane, I'm going to become a politician.
카사네, 난 정치가가 될 거야
I want to build a country where its people won't be monitored
국민을 감시하지 않는 정부와
and lied to by the government.
국민에게 거짓말하지 않는 나라를 만들고 싶어
I want to make life better for Bell Peppers.
벨 페퍼의 삶을 고민해주고
I want to research on the Other particles.
괴이 입자를 연구하고 싶어
But the Extinction Belt is gone.
단절의 띠가 사라졌잖아
There could be a way to turn people back to normal after metamorphosis.
혹시 괴이화된 인간을 되돌릴 수 있을지도 몰라
Yuito...
유이토
I'll create a better future.
난 정치가가 되어 미래를 창조할 거야
The OSF can do better.
토벌군은 더 훌륭한 조직이 되어야 해
We should be able to retire if we choose to.
자신만의 생각으로 소대를 탈퇴하다니
Even if you could, you wouldn't,
가능하다고 해도 소대를 탈퇴할 생각은 없지?
-right, Shiden? -Of course.
-시덴 -당연한 거 아니야?
You're the future chief after all.
네가 본부장이 될 때까지?
It has nothing to do with this.
그거랑 상관 없어
I don't know how far up I'll reach,
내가 어디까지 걸어갈 수 있을지 모르지만
but I'll try my best!
그래도 여전히…
Me too.
나도 그래
I'm not sure how much longer this body can hold up,
내 몸이 언제까지 버틸 수 있을지 모르지만
but before that,
그래도 그날이 올 때까지
I won't stop fighting.
여전히 전투하고 싶어
We aren't that different from Kasane when you think about it.
결국 우리도 달에 가고 싶어하는 카사네와 다를게 없잖아
Yuito must have his own plans as well.
유이토도 자신만의 계획이 있을 거야
He's not the kind who would settle down.
지금 상황에 만족하면서 살 녀석이 아니잖아
He might actually become a politician.
어쩌면 정치가의 길을 걸을지도 몰라
We can't let Kasane and Yuito get ahead of us.
카사네와 유이토에게 질 수는 없지
To think that ignorant brat will become a politician...
그 순진하던 녀석이 정치를 한다라…
Perhaps you could show him the way, General.
한수 가르쳐주시는 건 어떨까요? 장군님
That's right! You can be his mentor.
맞아, 유이토한테 개인과외 좀 해줘
How does that sound, General?
어때요? 장군님
That is a great idea, General.
아주 좋은 생각인데요, 장군님
Give it a rest.
나 좀 살려주라
I must go now and do my best to help.
난 내가 할 수 있는 일을 하기 위해 갈 거야
I wouldn't expect anything less from you.
참 너 답다
You could be a great politician.
정치가도 너한테 잘 어울려
Honestly, I'm not very sure about that.
사실 자신이 없지만
But I have made up my mind.
이미 결정 내렸으니까
Thank you, Kasane.
고마워, 카사네
I didn't do anything.
내가 뭘 도운 것도 없는데…
Honestly, I feel worried.
사실은 나도 많이 불안해
But even when I'm alone,
그래도 나 혼자 가는 거긴 하지만
I feel motivated knowing that everyone
너랑 함께 노력하는 애들 생각하면
is still giving their all for the world.
동력이 생겨
Perhaps it's changing the world is an inflated thought.
세상을 바꾼다는 것이 과장된 말 같지만
We've saved the world once,
세상을 구출했으니
I'm sure we can change it for the better.
세상을 바꾸는 것도 가능할 거야
I'm going to college while you are going to the Moon.
난 대학에 입학하고 넌 달에 가고
We will be a great distance between us,
비록 우리가 멀리 떨어져 있지만
but we are still in the same world.
결국 같은 세상에 살고 있는 거지
I'll leave this place in your care.
여긴 너한테 맡길게
Sure, you can count on me.
응, 나한테 맡겨
I'll live on.
나 이곳에서 열심히 살아갈 거야
Others have been spotted in area E-24.
E-24지역 괴이 출현
Haruka...
하루카
Alice Platoon, head to the area immediately.
앨리스 소대, 지금 당장 현장으로 출동해
Shiden Platoon, moving out.
시덴 소대 출동
Let's go, everyone.
좋아, 다들 가보자고
I'm coming with you.
나도 갈게
Are you going too?
너도 가려고?
I'm still a member of OSF.
나 아직은 토벌군의 일원이잖아
Each of us is a unique individual.
모두가 서로 다른 개체이지만
However,
그래도
people can be connected with each other.
사람과 사람 사이는 모두 연결될 수 있다
You can be alone, but not lonely.
아무리 혼자라고 해도 결코 절대 혼자가 아니다
YOU'VE RECEIVED A MESSAGE
(메시지 도착, 검사 완료)
YUITO SUMERAGI
(유이토 스메라기)
KAITO
(유이토)
No matter how far apart we are...
아무리 멀리 떨어져도
Even if we can't see each other...
만날 수 있는 곳까지 도착하지 못한다 해도
We are...
우리는…
♫I'm troubled by my own yearning♫
추구하는 동경에 사로잡혀
♫Unveil the blocked sun ray♫
아른거리며 앞을 막는 햇볕을 제껴
♫There's a stranger in me♫
There's a stranger in me
♫That I've never seen♫
여태 본 적이 없어
♫I can not soar in the sky without fear♫
공포는 묻어두고 하늘 높이 날 수 있을까
♫I'm spreading my wings♫
I'm spreading my wings
♫Dancing gracefully like a bird♫
예쁘게 춤추는 새들과
♫And gazing towards the scarlet sky♫
빨갛게 물든 하늘을 쳐다봐
♫I chased after the gust♫
강한 바람을 따라가
♫The scenery spreads into the ever-changing world♫
변해가는 세계에 경치가 퍼지고 있어
♫Inside the intertwined brilliance♫
뒤얽힌 빛 속에서
♫I'm still searching for tomorrow's direction♫
계속해 내일 걸어갈 길을 찾아
♫Tomorrow's in your hands♫
Tomorrow's in your hands
♫Don't tell me now you're afraid♫
Don't tell me now you're afraid
♫There's no time to waste♫
There's no time to waste
♫Go forward♫
나아가
♫Have no fear for anything♫
더 이상 아무것도 두려워하지 마
♫Now, let's go♫
함께 가
♫Into a brand new day♫
Into a brand new day